# **BRIAN HOANG**

Web Developer

# **INFO**

Phone: 07852786300

Email: bhoang35@gmail.com

Website: https://brian-hoang.com

## **KEY SKILLS**

- Intuitive Design
- Code Optimization
- UI Enhancement
- Project Management
- Issue Resolution

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### **Front-End Development**

- HTML5
- CSS3 (SASS, Flexbox, Grid)
- JavaScript (ES6, TypeScript)
- jQuery
- React (Redux, Gatsby, Router)

## **Back-End Development**

- PHP
- Node.js (Express)
- PostgreSQL
- Redis

#### Other

- Gulp
- Webpack
- Jest (Enzyme)
- Git (GitHub, Heroku)
- Photoshop
- Premiere
- After Effects

## **PROFILE**

Self-taught Web Developer with the ability to conceptualize and deliver responsive, user-friendly solutions effectively and efficiently. Helped curate the online experience of several businesses to gain and retain customers by creating appealing and informative content. Continue to improve skills individually as well as communally through meetups and hackathons.

#### **PROJECTS**

**Advocates for Animals** – React website built for an animal rights law firm connected to the WordPress REST API.

Used: React, React Router, ES6, SASS.

**MAGE Calculator** – Web app with a login system which detects faces within image URLs provided using Clarifai API.

Used: React, ES6, CSS3, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL.

**FoodApp** – Progressive web app that gives restaurant recommendations based on current or provided location. Uses Google Places and Zomato API.

Used: React, ES6, CSS3, Bootstrap.

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

**BAMM London** (April 2018) – Edited and translated several interviews for Shell regarding their products and brand in Vietnam, constructing a better understanding of the people and the market for the client.

**Barr Pictures** (August 2015 - Present) – Editing documentaries for a myriad of organisations that have to meet varying needs and goals, which have been showcased and aired across the globe.

**Fiorella Shoes** (February 2015 - Present) – Overseeing online business on ecommerce platforms as well as graphic design for their website and products that has helped drive up traffic on product pages and increase sales.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **GOLDSMITH'S UNIVERSITY OF LONDON (2011 -2014)**

BA Media and Communications (Second Class Honours Upper Division)